Guide to the Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted), 1910-1992 AIS.1996.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted)
1910-1992
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs
AIS.1996.16
52.75 Linear Feet
The collection contains both published and unpublished reports and studies of public projects and agencies that focus primarily on Pittsburgh and Allegheny County. Although limited, the collection also includes reports and studies on the city and county of Philadelphia, other areas in Pennsylvania, and some for other states and countries. Of particular note are the numerous annual reports and studies produced by departments and authorities within Pittsburgh and Allegheny County. Digital reproductions of selected reports are available online.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transfer from the University of Pittsburgh's Graduate School of Public and International Affairs Library (GISPIA) on June 6, 1996.
Related Material
Allegheny Conference on Community Development Collection, 1944-1993, AIS.1973.04, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
City Planning Commission, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1928-1962, AIS.1976.17, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1929-1985, AIS.1978.06, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
ACTION Housing, Inc. Records, AIS.2001.11, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Stephen Reichstein Papers,1923-1978, AIS.2012.01 Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Edward E. Smuts Papers, 1945-1981, AIS.2012.07, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh Records Relating to Phase I of the East Street Interchange Project, 1969-1971, AIS.1978.16, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh Records, 1937-1953, AIS.1966.08, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Arrangement
Series I: Reports on Allegheny County
Series II: Reports on Philadelphia (city and county)
Series III: Reports on Pennsylvania
Series IV: Reports on Pittsburgh (city)
Series V: Reports on Turtle Creek Valley (borough and region)
Series VI: Reports on Municipal Governments in Pennsylvania
Series VII: Reports by the University of Pittsburgh
Series VIII: Reports from other States
Series IX: Reports from Foreign Nations
Series X: Reports on Various Topics
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of selected reports will soon be available online.
Biography/History
The collection of assorted Public Administration Reports and Studies originated in the Library of the Graduate School of Public and International Affairs and consists primarily of reports produced for public administration projects and governance. Included are a myriad of redevelopment project planning reports, reports produced by state and local governments, and reports produced by researchers and center's at the University of Pittsburgh. The subjects of the reports and studies include: children's and youth services, employment, environmental impact, health care, education, housing, infrastructure, manufacturing and industry, parks and recreation, public safety, taxation, transportation, utilities, and more.
Previous Citation
Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted), 1910-1992, AIS.1996.16, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
This collection was previously known as "The Glidden Collection." Glidden Classification is a Library of Congress system for cataloging "Public Administration" reports and documents.
City planning -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia; Municipal government; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Politics and government; Allegheny County (Pa.) -- Politics and government; City planning -- Pennsylvania -- Turtle Creek (Pa.); Pittsburgh (Pa.); University of Pittsburgh; Transportation; Politics; Health and medicine; Government; Urban renewal -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Urban renewal -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia; City planning -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh
- Reports on Allegheny County, 1944-1985; I.
  - Port Authority of Allegheny County, 1951-1973; 1.
    - Advertising and Promotion Demonstration Program, Urban Mass Transportation Demonstration Project, Final Report, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, Allegheny County Transit and Traffic Commission, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Application to the Urban Mass Transportation Administration for a Capital Grant in re: Project No. PA-UTG-12, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appraisal of Transit Operations, Port Authority of Allegheny County, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Hearing on the Early Action Program Held by the Port Authority of Allegheny County, Volume I, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Hearing on the Early Action Program Held by the Port Authority of Allegheny County, Volume II, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Hearing on the Early Action Program Held by the Port Authority of Allegheny County, Volume III, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fifth Annual Report, Port Authority of Allegheny County, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County, 1972 Monthly Statistical Report, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Report and Recommendations; Transit Expressway and Patways, Port Authority Rapid Transit Committee, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Report of Allegheny County Mass Transportation Committee, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Report of General Manager, Port Authority of Allegheny County Transit Division, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Report on the Transportation and Parking Facilities in Connection with Proposed Permanent Site for the Pittsburgh Civic Light Opera, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - South Hills Transit Expressway Revenue Line, Preliminary Engineering Report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Statement, Findings and Recommendations of the Allegheny County Mass Transportation Study Committee, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Supplemental Report and Recommendations of the Port Authority of Allegheny County for an Integrated System of Mass Transportation in Allegheny County, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Survey of Waterborne Traffic Patterns and Waterside Public Terminal Facilities in the Allegheny County Area, Volume 1 Narrative Report, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Urban Development Program UA 243, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1946-1957; 2.
    - Highway Study in Allegheny County, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Recommended Standards for Recreational Facilities, Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Report of Refuse Disposal Committee, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Reporting on the Four County Industrial Inventory, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny County Planning Commission, 1947-1970; 3.
    - Land for Industry, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Master Plan of Airports, Allegheny County 1956, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Study of Facilities, Land and Commerce Oriented to the Inland Waterways Serving Allegheny County, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Allegheny County Regional Planning Council, 1972-1975; 4.
    - Juveniles in Jeopardy, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Justice Commission, Public Hearings, Summary of Testimony and Index, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Justice Commission, Public Hearings, Summary of Testimony and Index, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Justice Commission, Public Hearings, Summary of Testimony and Index, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Toward a Safer Community, An Analysis of Crime and Justice in Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Toward a Safer Community: Vol. No. 2, An Analysis of Crime and Justice in Allegheny County, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Human Sevice Commission, 1974; 5.
    - Considerations Surrounding Citizen Participation in the Delivery of Human Services in Allegheny County, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Toward a Living Renaissance, A Report of the Allegheny County Human Service Commission, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Health Department, 1969-1982; 6.
    - Annual Report, Allegheny County Health Department, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Article XIII, Smoke and Air Pollution Control, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Building a Healthier Community, Allegheny County Health Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Employee's Handbook, Allegheny County Health Department, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Improving the Environment, Allegheny County Health Department Division of Environmental Health, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Project Proposal, Communicable Disease Comprehensive Health Services, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Rules and Regulations, Article XIII- Air Pollution Control, Department of Health, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Health and Welfare Association of Allegheny County, 1963-1971; 7.
    - 50 Years, Health and Welfare Association of Allegheny County, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Cause for Concern, The Report of the Task Force on Youth Problems Reappraisal and Development Commission, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Day Care Services, Part IV of the Allegheny County Child Welfare Study, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Goals for Income Maintenance, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Report of the Task Force on Services to Families and Children to the Reappraisal and Development Commission, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Social Planning Aspects of the Community Renewal Program(CRP), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Social Services and Welfare Assistance in the Model Neighborhood, Part 1: Goals, Problem Analyses, Program Approaches, and Strategy, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Housing and Urban Development Department, 1967-1973; 8.
    - Model Neighborhood Program, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - The Model Cities Program, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Redevelopment Authority of Allegheny County, 1962-1969; 9.
    - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Redevelopment Authority of Allegheny County, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Urban renewal -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Solid Wastes Advisory Committee, 1969-1971; 10.
    - Proceedings: Solid Wastes Disposal Symposium, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Questions and Answers About Solid Waste Management in Allegheny County, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Solid Wastes Management Recommendations, A plan for immediate action, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1965-1979; 11.
    - A Time For Concern, The Status of the Elderly and Handicapped in Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Additional Open Space Analysis and Open Space Capital Needs, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny/Westmoreland Commuter Rail Study, Phases I and II Report, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - An Evaluation of the Car-Pool Public Transit Program, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - An Evaluation of the Car-Pool Public Transit Program, Appendix 2: Commuter Mode Choice Survey Results And Factors Influencing Mode Choice, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - An Evaluation of the Car-Pool Public Transit Program, Appendix 4: Matchee Survey Results, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Base Year Transit Analysis and Transit Network Calibration, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Calibration of the 1967 Arterial Highway Network for the Southwestern Pennsylvania Region, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cycle III Forecasting Methodology, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Environmental Planning Manual, A Manual of Environmental Guidelines for Regional and Local Planning, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Goods Movement Reconnaissance, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Low Paying Jobs Study, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Open Space Demand Model, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Physical and Man-Made Features of the Region, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Regional Open Space, A Regional Planning Study, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Standards and Regulations Applicable to Public School Building Construction Projects, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Status of Minority Group Employment in the Southwestern Pennsylvania Region, Preliminary Report, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Travel Surveys Coding Manual, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Truck Survey Procedures, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Vanpool Implementation Manual, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Allegheny League of Municipalities, 1970-1984; 12.
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Report of Wage & Salary Programs In the Municipalities of Allegheny County, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District, 1968-1975; 13.
    - Annual Report, Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Plan for Public Investment, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Bituminous Coal Industry in Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Western Pennsylvania Comprehensive Health Planning Association, 1973-1974; 14.
    - Annual Report, Comprehensive Health Planning Association of Western Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Guidelines for the Planning and Development of Emergency Medical Services in Western Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1978-1980; 15.
    - Annual Report, Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Planning Department, 1963-1970; 16.
    - Engineering Report For Board of County Commissioners, Proposed Allegheny County Refuse Disposal System, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Index of Environmental Reports, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1967-1973; 17.
    - Management of Urban Watersheds: An Assessment For Regulatory Action, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - The Application of a Light-weight, Geometrically-Flexible Transit Technology to a Rapid Transit System for Allegheny County, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1950-1978; 18.
    - Allegheny West Final Report, Part 1: Application for Loan and Grant, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - An Internship Report on the Allegheny Academic Instruction and Development Program of the Community College of Allegheny County, Allegheny Campus, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Community Involvement in a Desegregated Setting, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Demographic Changes, Enrollment Trends and the Future of Higher Education: Technical Report, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Proceedings of Local Government Conference on Air Pollution and Smoke Prevention Problems in Allegheny County, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Refuse Collection and Disposal Programs in Western Pennsylvania Political Subdivisions: A Survey, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Sampling, Field Work and Data Processing for a Study of Pediatric Health Care Patterns in the Twelve County Regions of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Special Municipal Charges to Finance Sewerage Facilities: A Survey of Sewer Rental Programs Adopted By Western Pennsylvania Political Subdivisions, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Refuse Disposal Problem in Allegheny County, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - ACTION-Housing, Inc., 1959-1980; 19.
    - A Plan of Operations for Urban Extension, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - A Summary of the Issues, Findings, and Recommendations of the Urban Renewal Impact Study, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Annual Report, Department of Aviation, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Background Memorandum on Developing Estimates of Public and Private Costs of Eliminating Slums and Blighted Areas in Allegheny County, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Interim Report on the Urban Renewal Impact Study, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Proposal for the Creation of the Allegheny Housing Rehabilitation Corporation, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Second Interim Report on the Urban Renewal Impact Study, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study, Administrative-Legal-Fiscal, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study, Coordinating Urban Renewal and Highway Planning and Development (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study, Final Reports, Recommendations and Findings, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study, Steep-Slope Renewal Its Opportunity and Challenge, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study, The genral Report, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Pennsylvania Economy League, 1949-1962; 20.
    - 101 School Districts in 22 Counties in Western PA: A Comprehensive Study of Local Effort, Resources and State Subsidies Measured in Terms of Market Value Millages and Resident Pupil Teaching Units, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - A Proposed Refuse Disposal System for Allegheny County, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - A Study of 1949-50 Expenditures and State-Aid per Pupil and per Teaching Unit Costs High School Tuition Charges 85 School Districts in 22 Counties in Western Pennsylvania, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny County's Automotive Fleet, Department of Property and Supplies, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - New Directions in Health and Welfare Planning, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Overall Economic Development Program for Allegheny, Beaver, and Westmoreland Counties, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Probable Locations for Sanitary Fills in Allegheny County, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Survey of the Allegheny County Transit and Traffic Commission, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study, Pennsylvania Economy League, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Urban Renewal Impact Study: Administrative-Legal-Fiscal, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Various Agency, 1939-1985; 21.
    - A Study of the Air Transportation Potential and Facility Requirements for Allegheny County Pennsylvania, 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, Allegheny County Jail, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, Allegheny County Works Department, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Conclusions of The Report on The Proposed Collection and Treatment of Municipal Sweage and Industrial Wastes, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Consumer's Guide to Consumer Services of Government and Private Agencies, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Directory of Occupational Wage Information, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Ground-Water Resources of the Valley-Fill Deposits of Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Master plan for Upper St., Clair Township, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania County Industry report: Allegheny County, Department of Commerce, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh Regional Limited Access Highways, Regional Industrial Development Corporation of Southwestern Pennsylvania, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Plans and Choices, Water Quality Mangement for The Southwestern Pennsylvania Region, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Proceedings Third University Conference, University Room Hotel Webster Hall, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Report Concerning Intercepting Sewerage Sewage Treatment and Disposal, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Report of the Special Committee to Investigate the Allegheny County Sanitary Authority, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Report On Community Planning and Integration in Allegheny County, Carnegie Institution of Technology, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Report Proposed Collection and Treatment Municipal Sewage and Industrial Wastes, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - RIDC(Regional Industrial Development Corporation of Southwestern Pennsylvania) Industrial Park in Allegheny County, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Street Cleaning Programs in Western Pennsylvania Jurisdictions: A Survey, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Summary Ground-Water Resources of Allegheny County, Department of Environmental Resources, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Summary Report of Session Four of The Allegheny Seminar, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Summary Report of Session Three of The Allegheny Seminar, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Summary Report on a Study of the Air Transportation Potentials and Facility Requirements for Allegheny County Pennsylvania, 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Text of Proposed Regional Parks Development Program Presentation, Regional Park Authority, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - The Effect of Staggering Work Hours in Pittsburgh's Central Business District on Traffic Volumes and Transit Ridership, Allegheny County Department of Planning and Development, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - The Hunger Crisis, An American Overview: The Need and Response in Allegheny County Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - The Rehabilitation Demonstration of The Allegheny County Board of Assistance, Department of Public Welfare, 1953-1958 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Large Itmes, 1965-1974; 22
    - Open space: a summary of findings of the regional open space study, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Physical resources: a summary of findings of the physical and man-made features of the region study, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Land for industry: a summary of findings and recommendations of the industrial land study, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Transportation advisory committee on the transit component of the regional transportation plan, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Regional recreation plan, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Reports on Philadelphia (city and county), 1950-1982; II.
  - Philadelphia County Political Subdivisions, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Annual Report 1981, Redevelopment Authority
  - Annual Report 1982, Redevelopment Authority
  - New Town Houses for Washington Square East, the Redevelopment Authority of the City of Philadelphia, 1964
  - Industrial Land Use Plan, 1950
  - Philadelphia 1968, International Federation for Housing and Planning
  - Center City Philadelphia, Philadelphia Planning Commission, 1960
  - Physical and Governmental Organization for Regional Sewage Facilities, 1960
  - Urban Renewal, Slum Clearance and Housing, 1958
  - A Review of Progress Under the Workable Program for Community Improvement for the Elimination and Prevention of Slums and Blight in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1966
  - Review of Selected Slum Clearance and Urban Renewal Activities Under the Administration of the Philadelphia Regional Office Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1961
  - A New Department to Plan, Develop, and Market Public Transportation Services in the Septa Area, 1970
  - Regional Parks, Parkways and Public Reservations, 1955
  - An Investigation of Location Factors Influencing the Economy of the Philadelphia Region, 1967
  - Technical Report #17, Community Renewal Program, 1965
  - Technical Report #15, Community Renewal Program, 1965
  - Technical Report #16, Community Renewal Program, 1965
  - Technical Report #14, Community Renewal Program, 1965